designtaxi.com 2008-12-17

# Privacy Policy - TAXI Design Network

» [Online Privacy Notice](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#one)  
» [What Information is Collected](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#two)  
» [How Information is Used](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#three)  
» [How Third-Parties are Involved](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#four)  
» [Application of Cookies](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#five)  
» [Commitment to Security](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#six)  
» [How End-Users can Access and Correct Information](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#seven)  
» [Special Notes to General Audience and Parents](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#eight)  
» [Essential Contact Information](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#nine)

**HILLS CREATIVE ARTS Pte Ltd ("HCA") Online Privacy Notice** [](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#top)  
This page set forth Hills Creative Arts Pte Ltd’s Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) for these web sites, http://www.HILLSCREATIVEARTS.com, http://www.ASTERIK.net and http://www.DESIGNTAXI.com (“Site”) and other residing sites under its domain. To better protect our end-user privacy, this notice explains our online information practices and the choices end-users can make about the way their information is collected and used at this HCA site. BY USING THIS WEBSITE, THE USER AGREES TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY.  

**What information is collected** [](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#top)  
At some HCA sites, end-users can order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online mailing lists, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include:

| **Individual End-Users** | **Corporate End-Users**  
---|---  
**For account creation and verification purposes**  
First/Last Name  
Email Address  
Residential Address  
City/ Country  
Telephone No. (w/country code)  
Profession  
Design Field  
Choice of HCA service plans and packages  
Credit Card Information 

**Other Optional Information**  
Alias/ Anonym  
Company/Institution Name & Address  
Website Title  
Website URL  
Fax No. (w/country code) 

**For end-user promotional purposes**  
Collection of portfolio works 

**Other required information**  
Includes interests and special requests with regards to use and/or purchase of products, programs and services.   

|  **For account creation and verification purposes**  
Registered Company Name  
Registered Company Address  
First/Last Name of Person-In-Charge  
Contact Information of Person-In-Charge 

Email Address  
Telephone No. (w/ext)  
Designation Held 

Company Email Address  
City/ Country  
Telephone No. (w/country code)  
Fax No. (w/country code)  
Corporate Design Category  
Choice of HCA service plans  
Credit Card Information 

**Other Optional Information**  
Website Title  
Website URL

**For end-user promotional purposes**  
Collection of 5-10 portfolio works  
Collection of advertisements for ad-rotation 

**Other required information**  
Includes interests and special requests with regards to use and/or purchase of products, programs and services.  
  
At certain HCA sites, end-users can submit information about other people. For example, end-users might submit a person's name and e-mail address to send an online reminder note or electronic greeting card and, if end-users order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, end-users might submit the recipient's name and address. In order to restrict unauthorized bulk email submission, only one email address will be allowed to be submitted by one end-user at any one time. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.

At certain parts of some of our sites, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to log in to user accounts; order products, programs, and services; or otherwise participate in the site's activities and offerings.

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when end-users visit our web pages such as the types of browsers end-users are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating systems end-users are using and the domain name of their Internet service providers.  

**How information is used** [](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#top)  
We may use the information end-users provide about yourself to fulfill their requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to their inquiries about our offerings, and to offer end-users other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to end-users.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with end-users, such as to notify end-users when they have won one of our contests or when we make changes to our subscriber agreements, to fulfill a request by end-users for an online newsletter, or to contact end-users about their account with us.

We may also use the information that end-users provide about others to enable us to send them their gifts or cards. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them.

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer end-users products, programs, or services.

If end-users choose to submit content for publication, we may publish their screen name and other information they have provided us with.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize their Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to evaluate consumer behavior, site traffic and usage, as well as a benchmark to better improve our products, programs, or services.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request. End-users are assured that personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to any third parties for any un-related commercial purposes, unknown to them prior to submission of their personally identifiable information.

Agents and contractors of HCA (e.g. “news contributors”) who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for HCA.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure end-users that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.

Certain HCA sites may disclose personally identifiable information to companies whose practices are not covered by this privacy notice, (e.g., other marketers, magazine publishers, retailers, participatory databases, and non-profit organizations) that want to market products or services to end-users. Such instances include disclosure of information for complimentary publishing in HCA annual compendiums and monthly newsletters. End-users have been informed and made agreeable of this complimentary service before they proceeded to submit their personally identifiable information. If a site shares personally identifiable information, it will provide end-users with an opportunity to opt out or block such uses.

HCA may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to end-users those products or services that may be of interest to end-users. If end-users prefer not to receive marketing information from this site.

Finally, HCA sites will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing end-users with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.  

**How Third-Parties are involved** [](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#top)  
Some of our sites contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

HCA sites sometimes may offer content (e.g., contests or promotions) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. HCA has no control over these parties' use of this information. The HCA site will notify end-users at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these parties will obtain such information.

Some HCA sites may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that end-users may see at its Web pages. Our privacy policy does not cover any use of information that a third-party ad server may have collected from end-users.  

**Application of Cookies** [](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#top)  
In order to enhance end-user experience, some of HCA pages use "cookies" to store preferences to facilitate navigation of the end-user. Cookies, by themselves, do not disclose e-mail addresses or other personally identifiable information unless end-users choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once end-users choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand consumer behavior, site traffic and usage; and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize their experience at our web pages (e.g. to recognize end-users by name when they return to our site), save their password in password-protected areas, and enable end-users to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer end-users products, programs, or services.  

**Commitment to Security** [](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#top)  
Appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures will be maintained to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.  

**How End-Users can Access or Correct Information** [](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#top)  
For instructions on how end-users can access the personally identifiable information that this HCA site has collected about end-users online, or how to correct factual errors in such information, please click on the login link on the top of this page. Different users will have different levels of access. For security reasons, end-users will have to log in with their preferred user ids and assigned passwords.  

**Special Note for General Audience and Parents** [](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#top)  
The site end-users are visiting is one of the HCA general audience sites. Content has been regulated and any explicit (e.g. violence or sexual) or unauthorized content, as decided by HCA, will be removed within forty-eight (48) hours once the HCA online team has been notified. It should be, however, noted that certain topics (e.g. nudity or racism) may be displayed on some articles and be recognized as authorized articles for artistic expression and not be treated as illegal materials.

Due to the artistic and creative nature of HCA, its sites and its end-users, certain display content may be controversial to certain audience. In instance of this happening, our audience is advised to contact HCA if they find any content undesirable and/or unsuitable for public viewing by using our feedback form at the end of each page. Upon removal, owner(s) of the removed content(s) will be notified accordingly after removal of content. They will then advance to submit new content(s) that will undergo another evaluation process before publishing. It is, however, important to note that request to remove content may be disregarded if we have evaluated and find the content suitable for display on our sites.  

**Essential Contact Information** [](http://www.designtaxi.com/privacypolicy.jsp#top)  
If end-users have any questions or concerns about the HCA online policy for this site or its implementation end-users may contact us by means of

Main Office  
51A Neil Road  
Singapore 088829

Postal Address  
Robinson Road Post Office  
PO Box 1140  
Singapore 902240  
Republic of Singapore 

Helpdesk Facsimile  
656.227.2902

Helpdesk Email Address (Privacy Policies)  
privacy@hillscreativearts.com
